<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://blog.suttna.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://blog.suttna.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-17T00:29:44+00:00</updated><id>https://blog.suttna.com/</id><title type="html">Suttna’s Blog</title><subtitle>Suttna's Journal</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Introducing Threads</title><link href="https://blog.suttna.com/slack/teams/threads/bot/suttna/2018/01/22/threads.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introducing Threads" /><published>2018-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://blog.suttna.com/slack/teams/threads/bot/suttna/2018/01/22/threads</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.suttna.com/slack/teams/threads/bot/suttna/2018/01/22/threads.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/threads/threads.png&quot; alt=&quot;App&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;we-are-really-proud-to-announce-that-suttna-now-supports-threads-&quot;&gt;We are really proud to announce that Suttna now supports threads 😌&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we started building Suttna, our main goal was to let users configure everything without leaving their messaging client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having that in mind, our first idea was to create a subset of dialogs where users would be able to just start a conversation running
a command (e.g. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@suttna configure&lt;/code&gt;) and Suttna will guide them according to what they wanted to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/threads/excelent-idea.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Excelent Idea&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the aspects that we didn’t thought at first was, how much distraction Suttna can create on a particular channel? How can we avoid distracting team members?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-should-i-get-20-message-notifications-if-im-not-even-configuring-a-checkin-right-&quot;&gt;Why should I get 20 message notifications if I’m not even configuring a checkin, right? 🤯&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that Suttna has a few months running checkins for companies around the globe, we understood that bot conversations are nice, buuut that they can be a bit annoying (just a bit 😅).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we started collecting feedback from several accounts and decided that it was time to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most users asked for a new config option to prevent Suttna messaging the channel right after a user finishes answering their questions,
so all the summaries would be posted to the channel only once when the checkin finishes, but that was a solution for only one scenario,
what about commands like &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@suttna configure&lt;/code&gt; for example? that would still trigger a notification for each new message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/threads/thinking.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Thinking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After thinking about other solutions, we decided to use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;threads&lt;/code&gt; (both messaging clients &lt;em&gt;Slack and MS Teams&lt;/em&gt; support them). Suttna will create a new thread when
entering a command and continue the conversation right there. This new flow won’t generate message notifications and won’t send too many messages to the group channel,
much better of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it wasn’t all a bed of roses, the Slack connector (&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/suttna/botbuilder-slack&quot;&gt;botbuilder-slack&lt;/a&gt;) that we’ve built for
&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Botbuilder&lt;/strong&gt; didn’t support threads, obviously that didn’t last too much, one week after our connector supports them 😍.
Check out here all of our contributions &lt;a href=&quot;http://github.com/suttna&quot;&gt;http://github.com/suttna&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We love to improve constantly, and your opinion really matter to us! (threads wasn’t an exception).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any feedback will be more than welcome so please, write to the team at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:feedback@suttna.com&quot;&gt;feedback@suttna.com&lt;/a&gt; if
you have anything to say.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Santiago Doldán</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.suttna.com/posts/threads/threads.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">New Web Application</title><link href="https://blog.suttna.com/2017/12/02/new-web-app.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Web Application" /><published>2017-12-02T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-12-02T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://blog.suttna.com/2017/12/02/new-web-app</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.suttna.com/2017/12/02/new-web-app.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/new-web-app.png&quot; alt=&quot;App&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago we rolled out a new web application that will let you search your checkin’s history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple customers have requested this feature, we invite everyone to try it. In order to login for first time
in you need to ask for a login link to Suttna. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@suttna login&lt;/code&gt; will do the work. Suttna will send you
a special link for you that can be used to access the web application for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new application will show you all the checkin events that are associated with the checkins you are participant of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can filter the events by the checkin they belong to and the time that the event happened. It’s also possible to
filter the events and get information from a specific person. This can be useful when trying to figure out what
you or other team member have done in a give time period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is just the begging of our web application. We want to get feedback from our users and improve based on that. Any
feedback will be more than welcome so please, write to the team at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@suttna.com&quot;&gt;feedback@suttna.com&lt;/a&gt; if
you have anything to say.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Martín Fernández</name></author><category term="web" /><category term="application" /><category term="new" /><category term="bot" /><category term="suttna" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.suttna.com/posts/new-web-app.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Suttna!</title><link href="https://blog.suttna.com/2017/12/01/welcome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Suttna!" /><published>2017-12-01T15:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-12-01T15:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://blog.suttna.com/2017/12/01/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.suttna.com/2017/12/01/welcome.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all we want to thank every single user that has been using Suttna so far. Your feedback has been invaluable to us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are going to use the blog for the following purposes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Announcements&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tips. How to take out the most from Suttna&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Technical information on how we’re building Suttna&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are about to announce some important changes to Suttna. You can stay tuned by subscribing to our newsletter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or issues your can always contact us at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@suttna.com&quot;&gt;support@suttna.com&lt;/a&gt; or just use the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@suttna support&lt;/code&gt; command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope that Suttna has been helpful for your team so far 😃&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Martín Fernández</name></author><category term="suttna" /><category term="welcome" /><category term="blog" /><summary type="html">Hello everyone!</summary></entry></feed>